五秒后开始
We're on in five seconds.
四 三 二
Four, three, two…
早上好 今天是星期五
Good morning. It's Friday.
欢迎各位收看本节目 我是主持人杰夫斯特灵
Glad you could join us. I'm your host, Jeff Stelling,
我身旁的是克里斯卡马拉和乔治卡特里克
here with Chris Kamara and George Cartrick.
（足球特辑）
我们将迎来本赛季的最后一个周末
As we head into the last weekend of the season,
关于西汉姆联俱乐部变化的谣言 有了一些新的消息
we have an update on those rumors of change at West Ham United.
但首先 我们先关注一下英冠
But first, we turn our attention to the championship
以及AFC里士满 我们爱说脏话的前同事效力的俱乐部
and AFC Richmond, the club of our former foulmouthed colleague…
即罗伊肯特
Roy Kent.
今晨的头条新闻是
The headline this morning is the news that
泰德拉索在本赛季托特汉姆比赛期间离场
Ted Lasso left in the middle of the Tottenham match this season
并非因为肠胃问题 而是因为惊恐症发作
not due to stomach problems, but because of a panic attack.
（吉列赞助 足球星期六）
拉索似乎要离开
Lasso appears to be leaving?
乔治
George?
拉索显然不适合当教练
Lasso's clearly not fit to coach.
拜托 乔治
Come on now, George.
-别这么冷血 -拜托 杰夫 得了吧
-Be compassionate. -Come on. Come on, Jeff. Come on.
比尔香克利会惊恐症发作吗  布莱恩克拉夫会吗
Would Bill Shankly have a panic attack, eh? Would Brian Clough?
-亚历克斯弗格森会惊恐症发作吗  -这么说不公平
-Would Alex Ferguson have a panic attack? -Be fair.
他当然不会了 听着 如果你的船遇袭了
No, of course he wouldn't. Look, if your ship's being attacked, right?
你跑到舰桥
And you run to the bridge,
你希望看到一位头脑正常的船长
you want to find a captain whose brain works,
而不是某个哭哭啼啼的家伙
not some big girl's blouse.
我想念罗伊
I miss Roy.
（雀巢 麦片）
（瑞贝卡即“老大” 泰德 别理那帮仇恨者）
（如果需要什么就打电话给我）
（莎伦医生语音留言）
嗨 泰德 记住 真相会让你自由
Hi, Ted. Remember, the truth will set you free,
但首先它会让你愤怒
but first it'll piss you off.
如果需要聊 请找我 祝周末好运
I'm here if you want to talk. Good luck this weekend.
（米歇尔拉索：嗨 泰德 看到新闻了 希望你没事）
（敲敲门）
（是谁 ）
（欧洲）
（欧洲什么 ）
（欧洲人民总算等到你起床了）
（哈哈 你显然没事）
（那么 是一大早有事 还是昨晚睡太晚 ）
（抱歉 这和我没关系 多谢你的关心）
（据称拉索因食物中毒离开球场）
（新线人表示离场的真实原因是惊恐症）
你们好
Hey, fellas.
-好 -这张不错
-Yeah. -Good one.
早安 苏珊
Morning, Susan.
早 你还好吗 泰德
Are you all right, Ted?
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
你确定
Are you sure about that?
（《星报体育版》 泰德的脑袋有问题 ）
（拉索的恐慌）
嗨 教练
Hey, Coach.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨 混蛋
Hey, wanker.
如果我父亲当年在诺曼底惊恐症发作
If my father had a panic attack at Normandy,
那我们今天都会说德语
we'd all be speaking German.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
好好做事 伙计 你会没事的
Just do the work, pal. You'll be all right.
你应该知道这是怎么回事吧
I assume you know what that was all about, yeah?
不知道
Nope.
花真好看 谁送的
Those are lovely. Who are they from?
艾德文阿库佛
Edwin Akufo.
“节哀顺变”
"Sorry for your loss."
他真体贴
That was thoughtful of him.
他一定听说你父亲过世的事了
He must've heard about your father's passing.
我没读完 “但我们会在卡萨布兰卡 为山姆准备一个很棒的家”
I've not finished. "But we will give Sam a very good home in Casablanca."
不过这还是个友善之举
Still, nice gesture.
那么 莱斯莉 关于山姆的决定 有什么动向吗
So, Leslie, any rumblings about which way Sam's leaning?
没有打探过 我试图假装淡定
Not a peep, and I'm trying to play it chill.
所以每次在走廊上碰见他 我只是冷漠点头
So whenever I see him in a hallway, I just give him a cool nod.
像是这样
You know, like this.
我的妈 真的很冷漠
Oh, shit. That was cool.
对吧 我在丹素华盛顿的电影里见过
I know, right? I saw it in a Denzel Washington movie,
我想：“好 我要据为己有”
and I thought, "I'm taking that."
不过情况不乐观
Still, it's not looking great.
嗨 有什么新消息 保罗舍里
Hey. What's the story, Paul Shorey?
泰德
Ted.
报道的事很遗憾 泰德
So sorry about the article, Ted.
没关系的 基莉
Oh, that's okay, Keeley.
你知道那句老话 没有不好的曝光
You know what they say. No such thing as bad publicity, right?
不过我认为这句话是错的
Although, I think they might've been wrong about that one,
很可惜 因为关于饮酒前 别喝啤酒的那句话 他们说得很对
which is a bummer 'cause they were spot on with the beer before liquor thing.
-给 老板 -谢谢 泰德
-Here you go, boss. -Thank you, Ted.
你知道大家都全心支持你
And you know that you have our full support.
我很感激
I appreciate that.
我还是懊恼自己没能做点什么
I still wish I could've done something
在那个混蛋特伦特克里姆发表报道之前
before that dick Trent Crimm posted the article.
那倒不用 特伦特是个好人 他只是在尽本职
Oh, no, come on. Trent's a good guy. He's just doing the gig.
不用担心 我会找报纸老板直接谈
Well, don't worry. I'm gonna speak directly to the owner of the paper
查清这个匿名线人的身份
and see who this anonymous source was.
别这样 不需要 事实上报道说的都是真的
Nah, come on, no need. Fact is, everything they said was true.
我与卡飞中尉不同的一点在于 我能应付真相
And unlike Lieutenant Kaffee, I actually can handle the truth.
好吧 我的建议是比赛前不接受媒体采访
Well then, my advice is no press until after the match.
我同意
I agree.
专注手头的任务 打败布伦特福德
Concentrate on the task in hand, beating Brentford.
是 因为如果我们输了 我会死的
Yes, because if we lose, it will kill me.
所以请别输球 泰德 求求你
Please don't lose, Ted. I beg you.
嘿 你别担心 希哥牛顿 我很有把握
Hey, don't you worry, Hig Newton. I'm on it like a bonnet.
天啊 真难吃
Oh, God. These taste like shit.
是的 昨晚没睡好 我很肯定
Oh, yeah. Well, it was a rough night, and I am now absolutely positive that
我把盐当成糖了 对不起
I switched the salt and sugar. I'm sorry about that.
不…
No, no, no.
不 味道颇有趣
No, it's interesting.
这是个偷偷发力的盐系贱人
She's a sneaky, salty bitch.
就像《飞跃情海》的海瑟洛克莱尔
Like Heather Locklear on Melrose Place, right?
-还真是呢 -对
-Oh, yeah. -Yeah.
对吧
Right?
-这样形容她太准确了 -对
-That's exactly how you'd describe her. -Yeah.
天 我的海瑟
Oh, Heather.
你好
Hello.
-我在那里不安全 -嗨
-I will not be safe out there. -Hey.
（山姆 我等不及看你穿上这身衣服）
（希望你别介意 我为你选了号码 艾德文阿库佛）
（奥比桑亚）
（反转金字塔）
好吗
All right?
罗伊在吗
Is Roy here?
没听见不满的闷哼声
I don't hear any grunting.
-嗨 早上好 -早上好 内特
-Hey, morning. -Morning, Nate.
罗伊在吗
Is Roy here?
不在
No.
读了这个没
You seen this?
是 太糟了
Yes. It's awful.
-是的 -对 很糟糕
-Yeah. -Yeah. It was awful.
是的
Yeah.
罗伊
Roy--
杰米在找你
Jamie's looking for you.
是吗
Oh, is he?
喂
Oi!
塔特
Tartt!
我
Me?
去那边 行吧
Through there? Yeah.
等等 能不能先让我说一件事
Wait. Can I just say something first?
好的 好主意
Yeah, okay. That's a good idea
因为等我跟你了结后 你一颗牙都不会剩
'cause when I'm done, you won't have any teeth left,
没有牙齿 你说不了话
and you'll need them for the talking bit.
是 好吧
Right. Yeah, okay.
在瑞贝卡爸爸的葬礼上 我告诉基莉我仍然爱着她
So, at Rebecca's dad's funeral, I told Keeley that I still loved her.
那是不对的 我不该那么做
It was wrong, and I shouldn't have done it,
但我不习惯和死人同处一室
but I ain't used to being around dead people.
我受影响了 在情绪上 你明白吗
It just-- It did something to me, emotionally, you know?
但仍然…我不该那么做 那是错的
But I still-- I shouldn't have done it, and it was wrong,
我希望你知道我尊重你
but I just need you to know that I respect you,
我尊重基莉 也尊重你们的感情
and I respect Keeley, and I respect your relationship,
我再也不会做那种事了
and I will never ever do anything like that ever again.
该死
Fuck!
抱歉 你们进来时我僵住了
Sorry. I kind of froze when you two came in here,
我不知道该做什么
and I just didn't know what to do.
好吧
All right.
不 听起来确实很有帮助 充满同情心
Yeah, no, it definitely sounds both helpful and compassionate.
但我觉得
But I don't think that
你主持拉索教练和 著名心理医生的心理咨询
you moderating a session between Coach Lasso and a celebrity psychiatrist
不是此刻最好的选择
is the best move right now.
他的所有注意力都在布伦特福德比赛上
All his attention is on Brentford.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
去死吧 皮尔斯摩根
Fuck you, Piers Morgan.
我的老天爷
Holy fucking shit!
天
Oh, my…
围过来
Circle up!
谢谢 教练
Thank you, Coach.
嗨
Hey, fellas.
开始之前 我想和你们谈一谈
Before we get started here, I wanted to talk to y'all about
今早你们在报纸上读的报道
the article you saw in the paper this morning.
其实你们应该是在手机上读的
Actually, y'all probably saw it on your phones.
我仍然订报纸 因为
I still get the paper, 'cause, well,
无法把手机上的漫画剪下来
you can't cut cartoons out of a phone, right?
对 但你可以截屏然后发出去
Yeah, but you can screenshot them and text them.
这是版权侵犯 哥们
That's copyright infringement, bruv.
-这样啊 -我明白你的话 佐豪
I hear you, Zoreaux,
但截屏画面没法挂在冰箱上
but you can't hang a screenshot on a fridge either.
我的冰箱有内置电视
My refrigerator has a television.
对 我的好像也是同款
I think I have the same one.
-我买的地方是… -重点是
-I bought it-- -The point is,
你们从某处得知了一件事
y'all found out about something from somewhere,
但其实你们应该先从我这里得知它
when you should've found out about it from me first.
我选择不告诉你们 这很愚蠢
But I chose not to tell y'all, and that was dumb.
各位 我们每一天都在做各种选择
You know, fellas, we make a lot of choices in our lives every single day,
从“我真的要吃 一种名为希腊式酸奶的东西吗 ”
ranging from, "Am I really about to eat something called Greek yogurt?"
到“我应该离开家人 去地球另一边工作吗 ”
To, "Should I leave my family and take a job halfway around the world?"
我选择不对你们坦诚 这不是好的选择
Me choosing not to be forthright with y'all, that was a bad choice.
但我不能浪费时间 懊悔过去的选择
But I can't be wasting time wishing for a do-over on all that.
因为选择不是那样的 对 先生
'Cause that ain't how choices work. No, sir. No.
那个选择和我的芝加哥公牛球迷外套
That choice, and my Chicago Bulls Starter jacket
我大二时让詹妮尔罗德斯借走的那件
that I let Janelle Rhodes borrow my sophomore year 'cause
因为她把番茄酱洒在自己身上 看起来像是中枪了
she spilled ketchup all over herself, and it looked like she'd been shot,
这两样东西是我无法收回的
those are two things I ain't getting back.
因为每一个选择都是一次机会
'Cause every choice is a chance, fellas.
我没有给自己一个机会 去努力与你们建立信任
And I didn't give myself the chance to build further trust with y'all.
用伟大的加州洛杉矶大学 篮球教练约翰欧比旺甘道夫的话来说
To quote the great UCLA college basketball coach, John Obi-Wan Gandalf,
“先生们 我们的选择远比我们的能力
"It is our choices, gentlemen, that show what we truly are,
更能展现真实的自我”
far more than our abilities."
我希望你们原谅我所做的事
Now, I hope y'all can forgive me for what I've done.
因为我绝对不希望
'Cause I sure as heck wouldn't want
你们任何人对我隐瞒什么
any of y'all to hold anything back with me.
-不 教练 我们支持你 -我们支持你 教练
-Nah, we got you, Coach. We got you. -We got you, Coach.
对 没事的 老大
Yeah, no problem, gaffer.
我们找到内鬼后
And when we sniff out the rat,
请允许我们用塞满肥皂的袜子 塞进那人的胸膛和腹部
permission to take socks full of soap to their stomach and chest?
我们会找到他 狠狠揍他
We're gonna find 'em and fuck 'em up!
-对 -我们会杀了他
-Yeah! -We'll kill him!
跟着钱走
Follow the money!
不 各位 听我说 我不能让这种想法生肝发牙
No, fellas, look. I'm gonna nip that talk in the butt right now.
“生根发芽” 不是“生肝发牙”
It's "bud" not "butt," Coach.
是吗 因为是说花朵
It is? 'Cause of flowers, right?
园艺学的比喻
Horticulture, baby!
这样比较说得通 谢谢指正
That makes more sense. I appreciate that. Thank you.
听着 先生们 我们需要专注于 更有建设性的东西
No, look, gentlemen. I want us to focus on something a little bit more productive,
比如练习伟大的内特的伪九号战术
like working on Nate the Great's false nine.
-听起来如何 好的 -是 好的
-How's that sound? Okay, good. -Yes. Yeah.
开始前还有什么问题吗
Okay, anybody got any questions before we get started?
-我有个问题 -是 杰米 请说
-Yeah, I got one. -Yeah, Jamie, what do you got?
那边的东西要怎么办
What are we gonna do with that fucking thing there?
是 问得好
Yeah, that's a good point. Okay.
这样好了 我们去北区
Well, tell you what, let's all head to the north field,
如果你们快点 就可以算是今天的有氧运动
and if you guys hustle, that'll count as our cardio for today, yeah?
快跑 快…
Scram! Whistle! Whistle!
请进
Come in.
这是怎么回事
What's this?
这是《吉祥物偶像大赛：半决赛》
This is Mascot Idol: Semifinals.
我们的新吉祥物将从这两位参赛者中诞生
One of these two contestants will be our new mascot.
会是梅西灰狗还是蒂娜菲狗呢
Will it be Macy Greyhound or Tina Feyhound?
可爱 它们都来自白金汪宫
Are they all from Barkingham Palace?
对
Yep.
坎贝尔小姐是收容所负责人
Miss Campbell here runs the shelter.
伦敦的优质全女性狗养殖场 苏西坎贝尔 很高兴认识你
London's premier all-female dog breeder. Suzi Campbell. Nice to meet you.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
我是你的铁杆粉丝
Huge fan.
这样啊 谢谢
Oh, thanks.
铁杆粉丝
Huge fan.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在是不是不方便
Is now a bad time?
不会 可以给我们一点时间吗
No. Could you give us a minute, please?
好 没问题
Sure.
天啊
Wow.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
遇到什么烦心事吗
Something wrong?
其实 是遇到了爽心事
Actually, something is incredibly right.
给伴伴提供资金的机构
The money people that back Bantr,
想为我投资开设属于我的公关公司
they wanna finance me opening my own PR firm.
天啊
Oh, my God!
很惊喜吧
I know, right?
我需要建议
I need some advice.
你找我谈 而不是泰德或罗伊 我受宠若惊
I'm flattered that you came to me instead of Ted or Roy.
他们在训练
They're at training.
还有瑞贝卡
Well, instead of Rebecca then.
我最不敢告诉的人是她
She's the one I'm afraid of telling.
我很高兴自己在名单上
I'm happy to be on the list.
我很怕
I'm scared.
听着 这很正常
Well, look. That is perfectly natural.
当老板是很吓人的事
It can be terrifying becoming a boss.
不 我怕的是告诉瑞贝卡我要离开
No. I'm scared of telling Rebecca I'm leaving.
有道理 因为她让人心生敬畏
Oh, right. Because she's so intimidating.
不 她是我最好的朋友之一
No. She's one of my best friends.
说得没错 而你的离开
Oh, yes. Yes, yes, yes. And you leaving would be
是一场通常只有希腊神话 才会出现的惊人背叛
a betrayal on a level usually reserved for Greek mythology.
不
No.
我只是不想显得自己不知感恩
I just-- I don't want to appear like I'm not grateful
她在这里为我提供了如此难得的机会
for the amazing opportunity she's given me here.
基莉 好的导师会希望你开创新人生
Keeley, a good mentor hopes you will move on.
伟大的导师则知道你一定会做到
A great mentor knows you will.
我喜欢这句话
I like that.
是吗 我刚刚编的
Yeah? Just made it up.
天啊
Wow.
我告诉艾德文阿库佛 我会在周日比赛后给他答案
I told Edwin Akufo I would give him my answer after the match on Sunday.
这是否意味着你已经做了决定
Does this mean you've made a decision?
是的
I think so.
-如何  -我不知道
Yes? I don't know.
傻子才不去呢 对吧
I'd be crazy not to go, right?
山姆 你想得太多了 放松
Samuel, you're overthinking this. Relax.
别试图找到答案 让答案找到你
Stop looking for the answer and let the answer come to you.
如果你敞开心扉 宇宙会给你一个信号
If you open yourself to it, the universe will give you a sign.
爸爸 别怪我直说
Daddy, with all due respect,
这么重要的决定 留给宇宙是不是太草率了
isn't this decision too important to be left to the universe?
宇宙向来为我指明对的方向
The universe has always put me on the right path.
宇宙让我和你母亲结婚 让我在2009年买比特币
The universe told me to marry your mother and to buy Bitcoin in 2009.
2009年啊
2009!
好的 爸爸 我会留心注意 宇宙有没有发出信号
Okay, Dad. I'll keep an eye out for any messages from the universe.
-我爱你 -我爱你
-I love you. -I love you.
（奥比桑亚）
今天早上杰米为他在葬礼上 对你说的话向我道歉了
This morning, Jamie apologized to me for what he said to you at the funeral.
我什么都没说
I didn't say anything.
我知道 他说那是他的决定
I know. He said he did it on his own.
你做了什么
What did you do?
你觉得呢
What do you think I did?
揍他
Punched him.
-用头撞他 -继续猜
-Headbutted him. -Keep going.
你杀了他吗
Did you murder him?
没有 更糟 我原谅了他
No. Worse. I fucking forgave him.
是不是很恶心
It's disgusting, innit?
不 我很为你自豪
No. I'm really proud of you.
我完全支持你
I fully support that.
等等 我也有新闻
Wait. I've got some news too.
拜托 别这样 别告诉我 泰德也对你发动进攻
For fuck's sake. Don't tell me Ted tried to get off with you and all.
为伴伴提供资金的风投公司
The VC that back Bantr,
想为我投资开办属于我的公关公司
they want to finance me opening my own PR firm.
该死的老天爷 这是大新闻
Holy fucking shit. That is huge.
你要当行政总裁了 太棒了
You are a fucking CEO and shit. That's amazing.
我知道
I know.
我好爱你
I love you so much.
瞧瞧你 老板
Look at you. The boss.
没时间再陪我了
Not gonna have time for me anymore.
闭上你的嘴
Shut your pretty mouth.
稍等 是简
Just need a second. It's Jane.
你们怎么样了
How's all that going?
我们分手了
We broke up.
我们又复合了
We're back on.
请用 孩子们
Here you go, boys.
谢谢 梅
Thanks, Mae.
不用放在心上 泰德
Don't worry about it, Ted.
人们很快就会忘了 向来如此
It'll all wash out in a cycle. It always does.
谢谢你 梅
Thank you, Mae.
反正我已经看完了
I was finished anyway.
我们要开香槟
We're opening the champagne.
什么 我们要等到非常特别的场合才开
What? No, I thought we were saving that for something really, really special.
你妈妈搬回北部时我们没开
Well, we didn't open it when your mum moved back up north.
英国在欧洲歌唱大赛得零分时没开
We didn't open it when England got zero points in the Eurovision.
邻居开车碾死自家蛇的时候也没开
And we didn't open it when the neighbor ran over their own snake.
那件事太可怕
That was nasty.
所以今晚必须喝 小心
So we are drinking it tonight. Duck.
好耶
Yay.
该死
Shit!
莉兹刚把《名利场》的文章预览发过来
Lizzy just sent over a preview of the Vanity Fair article.
完了 他们最好别用我微笑的照片
Oh, shit. They better not have used any pictures of me smiling.
说得像有那种照片一样
Like that exists.
天啊
Wow.
（基莉琼斯 顶层女强人）
不好
Oh, no.
他们没有用有你的照片
They didn't use any of the pictures with you in them.
见鬼 真抱歉 罗伊 这样不对
Shit, I'm so sorry, Roy. That is not cool.
-我会联系他们改回来 -千万别
-I'm gonna reach out and change that. -Don't you dare.
什么都别改
Don't you change a fucking thing.
你看上去很强大 你美极了
You look powerful. You're fucking gorgeous.
你看起来像个性感老板
You look like a BILF.
这样吗 那给我展示一下吧
Oh, yeah? Go on, show me, then.
那么
So…
你打算回应吗
Are you gonna say anything?
最终会的
Well, I mean, eventually, yeah.
这么多年来 你应该也注意到了 我是个很多话的人
You may have noticed through the years I can be quite loquacious.
不 我是说对内特
No. To Nate.
匿名线人
The anonymous source.
天啊 你为什么觉得是内特
Wow. What makes you think it was Nate?
对
Yeah.
你懂我的哲学
Well, you know my philosophy
在猫咪 宝宝和道歉上 教练
when it comes to cats, babies and apologies, Coach.
只能等 不能求
You gotta let 'em come to you.
你不会等到的
That's not gonna happen.
有的人就是需要推一把
Some people need a little push.
是 我不会推任何人
Yeah. Well, I ain't pushing nobody.
我觉得推一把有用
I think it'll help.
内特不会有事的
Nate will be fine.
不 是对你有用
No. It'll help you.
教练 如果你继续将一切埋在心里
Coach, you keep trying to hold all this in,
我担心你憋得连胡子都会掉
I'm afraid your mustache is gonna pop off.
那我会看起来像《宿醉》那个人
Then I'll look like that fella from The Hangover.
布莱德利库柏
Bradley Cooper.
你对我真温柔
You're too good to me.
我喜欢你的胡子
And I like your mustache.
嗨 宝贝
Hi, babe.
嗨
Hi.
你有时间吗
Have you got a second?
当然
Of course.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不 别道歉
No, don't be.
这是好事
It's good.
你帮这只熊猫成长为狮子
You helped this panda become a lion.
我真为你自豪
I'm so proud of you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的天
Holy fucking shit.
不好 怎么了
Oh, no. Now what?
鲁伯特刚买下西汉姆联俱乐部
Rupert's just bought West Ham United.
（西汉姆的新老板）
不
No.
我竟然我以为他把俱乐部股份给我
And to think for a second, I thought him giving me his shares in the club
是出于善意
was a kind gesture.
其实 我反而安心了 发现
You know, I'm actually quite reassured to find out
他仍然是那个自私 诡计多端的混蛋
that he is still just a selfish conniving cock.
对 这确实让宇宙恢复了某种平衡 对吧
Yeah. It does return a certain balance to the universe, doesn't it?
答应我你不会去为他打工
Promise me you will not go and work for him.
他请不起我
He can't afford me.
里士满是我的足球俱乐部 你很清楚
Richmond is my football club. You know that.
如果我们晋级的话
Well, that's if we get promoted.
也许你就不会想为我们工作了
You might not want to work with us.
那倒是
That's fair.
关于当老板 一个小建议
A bit of advice for being a boss.
聘请你最好的朋友
Hire your best friend.
去你的
Fuck you.
我又要哭了
Now I'm crying again.
有人要票吗
Anyone want a ticket?
-梅 你好吗  -嗨…梅
-All right, Mae? -Oi, oi, Mae!
-加油 里士满 -加油 里士满
-Come on, Richmond! -Come on, Richmond!
加油 里士满
Come on, Richmond!
加油 打败他们
You get out there and you beat 'em.
我们必胜 好吗
We'll smash it, right?
加油 踢得他们落花流水
You get them. Fuck 'em.
加油 教练
Go, Coach.
下午好
Good afternoon.
-下午好 -下午好
-Good afternoon. -Afternoon.
（成功金字塔）
好 你们今天准备好 使用内特的伪九号战术了吗
All right. Y'all good to go on running Nate's false nine today, yeah?
不这么做就太蠢了
Well, you'd be fools not to.
好
All right.
-对 我们得试一试 -为什么现在改变
Yeah, we ought to give it a shot. Why change it now?
我同意
I agree.
你的办公室又被抢走了
Did you get kicked out of your office again?
不是 临时搬迁 因为要换地毯
No, no. Temporary relocation while they change the carpet in there.
到处都是狗大便
It was absolutely covered in dog shit.
懂了 我有相同经历
Oh, yeah. No, been there, done that.
好的 在我们上场前 还有谁想说点什么吗
Okay. Well, anybody else got anything they wanna talk about before we head out there?
是
Yeah.
我可以…
I could…
听一听…
use some…
建议
advice.
等等
Hold on.
罗伊 你是说你想成为钻石狗
Roy, are you saying you wanna become a Diamond Dog?
才不是 我只是说我不介意
Fuck no. I'm just saying I wouldn't mind
留在屋里
being in the room
听你们开会
whilst it fucking happens.
好的 可以 那不如 发一张一次性游客通行证
Yeah. Okay. Well, how about a one-time visitor's pass
给这位友情客串狗
for our junkyard dog here, yeah?
钻石狗 集合了
Diamond Dogs, mount up!
是 等等
Yeah. I gotcha.
-是 我留在这里就好 -好的 好主意
-Yeah. I'm just gonna stay put. -Okay. Good idea. Yeah.
吃一堑长一智 对吧 谢谢 艾拉妮丝
You live, you learn, right? Thank you, Alanis.
好了 罗伊
All right. Roy.
请吠叫吧
Bark away.
记不记得我说过 那次不得不和基莉去拍照
Remember I told you I had to do that photo shoot thing with Keeley?
-对 记得 -是的…
-Yeah, we got it. -Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah.
我知道我说自己讨厌做那种事
I know I said I fucking hate doing those things,
我确实讨厌做那种事
and I do fucking hate doing those things.
但结果
But in the end,
他们没有用任何有我的照片
they didn't use a single picture with me in it.
这伤害了我的
And it hurt my…
感情
feeling.
-明白 -对
-Oh, yeah. -Yeah.
五年级时 我不能参加班级拍照
In year five, I was not allowed in the class photo
因为我患了一种罕见的微笑过敏症
because I developed a rare smile allergy.
情况不同
Not the same situation.
问题是…
The thing is…
她那么美
she looked so fucking great.
独自一人
On her own.
没有我
Without me.
如此自然
So natural.
我…
I--
如果我在照片里 反而会变得很奇怪
It would've actually been fucking weird if I was in the pictures.
然后 在瑞贝卡爸爸的葬礼上
And then at Rebecca's dad's funeral,
该死的杰米塔特告诉她自己还爱着她
Jamie fucking Tartt tells her he's fucking in love with her.
而他还活着
And he's still alive?
对 我没有揍死他 而是原谅了他
Yeah. Instead of beating him to death, I fucking forgave him.
我仍然很愤怒
I'm still fucking furious about it.
好的 罗伊 感谢你对我们吠叫
Okay. Well, Roy, we appreciate you barking at us.
其实 我也要坦白一件事
There's something I have to confess as well.
请说 内特狗
Go ahead, Nate-dawg.
罗伊
Roy,
基莉和我那天购物时 我吻了她
when Keeley and I went shopping the other day, I kissed her.
是 她告诉我了
Yeah. She told me about it.
没关系
It's okay.
我吻了她 我吻了你的女友
I kissed her. I kissed your girlfriend.
不要紧
We're good.
杰米不过是和她说话 你就想杀了他
All Jamie did was talk to her, and you wanted to kill him.
你难道不想至少用头撞撞我什么的
Don't you at least wanna headbutt me or something?
你犯了个错 内特 不用放在心上
You made a mistake, Nate. Don't worry about it.
不 我活该被撞头
No, no, I deserve to be headbutted.
我很愿意用头撞你 内特
I'd be happy to headbutt you, Nate.
好吧 我觉得到此为止
Okay, you know what? I think that's enough right now.
我们还有活要干 钻石狗散会
We got work to do, yeah? Diamond Dogs dismount?
等等 所以有时该死的钻石狗开会
Wait. So sometimes the fucking Diamond Dogs
不过是聊聊家常
is just chatting about shit,
不需要解决什么问题 什么也不会改变
and no one has to fucking solve anything and nothing fucking changes?
有时是的
Sometimes. Yeah.
酷
That's cool.
天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, Oh, my God.
太好了
Yes, yes, yes!
这是两支球队的第83次对战
It's the 83rd clash between these two teams
而今天的这场比赛事关重大
and there's never been more at stake.
布伦特福德领先 但里士满
Brentford with the lead but Richmond
仍然采取不寻常的伪九号队形
are still in their unusual false nine formation.
我不喜欢 阿尔洛 这是本赛季 最后一场晋级赛
I don't like it, Arlo. The last match of the season for promotion.
在这个时机用新战术很冒险
It's a funny time to be pulling out a new strategy.
里士满想在中场之前追平
Richmond trying to even it up before the half,
但他们失去控球了 布伦特福德人数占据优势
but they give away possession, and Brentford have numbers.
好
Yeah!
-该死 -2比0 布伦特福德领先
-Fuck! -And that's 2-nil to Brentford.
在这么晚的阶段 这么要紧的关头采取新招数
You try new tactics this late with this much at stake
大家都不开心
and everyone loses their heads.
别冲 需要我说多少次 留在后面
Stay back! How many times do I have to fucking tell ya? Stay back.
没事
It's all right.
嘿 我们没事的
Hey. We're all right!
没关系 加油
It's okay! Come on now!
中场休息
And it's halftime
这场西伦敦本地球队的德比之战扣人心弦
of what has been a pulsating West London derby.
布伦特福德2比0领先
Brentford lead 2-nil,
里士满正看着黄金机遇
and Richmond are letting a golden opportunity
从指尖溜走
slip through their fingers.
我直话直说 情况不妙 好吗
I'ma shoot y'all straight. This is bleak, yeah?
瞧瞧外面
I mean, look at it out there.
看上去像一幅 刻画男性忧伤气质的文艺复兴画作
Looks like a Renaissance painting portraying masculine melancholy.
怎么办 我们该做什么
Okay, so now what? What we gonna do?
我们应该放弃伪九号战术
We should abandon the false nine.
如果球员知道自己在做什么 那个战术会有效
It'd work if we had players who knew what the fuck they were doing.
我不同意 内特 我们应该坚持
Yeah, I don't agree, Nate. You know, I think we gotta stick with it, man.
我们刚才有45分钟弄清楚什么是错误行为
You know, they just had 45 minutes to figure out what not to do. Yeah?
罗伊 你觉得呢
What do you think, Roy? You should ask them.
他们才是踢球的人
They're the ones out there actually doing this shit.
是 好的
Yeah, all right.
好了 各位
All right, fellas.
教练团和我讨论了一下 我们想知道你们的意见
Coaches and I are having a little debate and wanna get y'all's take on it.
我们应该坚持采用伪九号战术 还是改变战术
Should we stick with the false nine or switch it up?
战术没问题 我们完全有能力执行
The tactic is sound, and we're all perfectly capable of executing it.
可以的
It will work.
嘿 如果杨马斯这么说 那一定是真的 对吧
Hey, if Jan Maas says it, you know it's the truth, right?
我不会说假话
I wouldn't lie to you.
比如 佐豪 你应该挡下第一个进球的
For instance, Zoreaux, you should have saved that first goal.
哥们
Bro.
好的 决定了 我们继续用内特的伪九号战术
Okay. It's been decided. We're gonna stick with Nate's false nine.
-来吧 凑过来 加油 -加油 灰狗
-Now, come on. Bring it in. Let's go. -Here we go, Greyhounds!
嘿 队长
Hey, Captain?
一起吗
You gonna join us?
（相信）
数到三一起说里士满 一 二 三
Richmond on three. One, two, three…
里士满
Richmond!
（胜利永驻）
加油 里士满
Here we go, Richmond!
嘿 内特
Hey, Nate.
嘿
Hey.
一切还好吗
Everything okay?
是的 泰德 一切都很好
Yes, Ted. Everything is okay.
怎么了 我做了什么
What is it? What'd I do?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
拜托 你对我很生气 我想知道原因
Oh, come on, man. You're mad as hell at me. I just wanna know why.
我有什么该改进的
Huh? What have I got to learn here?
-你想知道你做了什么  -是 谢谢
-You wanna know what you did? -Yeah, please.
好的 那我就告诉你
Okay. I'll tell you what you did.
你让我感觉自己是世界上最重要的人
You made me feel like I was the most important person in the whole world.
然后你抛弃了我
And then, you abandoned me.
仿佛一下子把灯熄灭
Like you switched out a light, just like that.
我竭尽全力 试图让你再关注我
And I worked my ass off, trying to get your attention back.
向你证明自己
To prove myself to you.
让你再次喜欢我
To make you like me again.
但是我越是努力 你越不在意
But the more I did, the less you cared.
就像我是透明人一样
It was like I was fucking invisible.
我在圣诞节给你的照片 你都没有摆在办公室里
You haven't even got the photo I gave you for Christmas up in your office.
只挂了一幅愚蠢美国人的照片
Just a picture of dumb Americans.
现在你要用内特的伪九号战术 这样当球队踢得不好
Now you're gonna play Nate's false nine, so when the team fuck up,
他们一定会的 你就可以怪罪我
which they will, hey, you can blame it on me.
不行 想得美
Well, no. Fuck that.
所有人都爱你
Everybody loves you.
伟大的泰德拉索 我认为你就是个笑话
The Great Ted Lasso. Well, I think you're a fucking joke.
没了我 你一场比赛都赢不了
Without me, you wouldn't have won a single match.
他们会让你回堪萨斯 那才是属于你的地方
They would've shipped your ass back to Kansas, where you belong.
和你儿子待在一起
With your son.
因为你绝对不属于这里
'Cause you sure as hell don't belong here.
但是我不同 我属于这里
But I do. I belong here.
我的一切不是别人送给我的 好吗 这是我努力得到的
This didn't just fall into my lap, all right? I earned this.
我知道 内特
I know you did, Nate.
很抱歉 我没有表达出你对我有多重要
And if I didn't tell you how important you were to me enough, I'm sorry about that.
别 你知道吗 你满口谎言
No, no. You know what? You're full of shit.
去你的 泰德
Just fuck you, Ted.
落后两分的里士满坚持用伪九号战术
Richmond down two, sticking with their false nine formation
布伦特福德在进攻
as Brentford are on the attack.
克里斯 里士满是不是已经没有时间 扭转局面 掌控未来了
Chris, is time running out on Richmond's chances to control their future?
如果你认为时间是一个线性概念 阿尔洛 那就对
Only if you think of time as linear, Arlo.
是 克里斯 我是这么认为
Yes, Chris. I do.
罗哈斯的攻势不错
Good pressure from Rojas.
塔特传得好
That's lovely from Tartt.
奥比桑亚拿球
Obisanya is in.
他射门得分了
He scores!
多亏了奥比桑亚的进球
And thanks to that Obisanya goal,
里士满仍有希望晋级
Richmond's hopes for promotion are still alive.
加油…上啊 来 再来一个
Let's go! Let's go! Come on! One more!
天啊
Oh, my God!
伪九号战术就是这么用的 阿尔洛
That's how you play a false nine, Arlo.
中场放满人 井井有条 寻找机会 做得好
Pack the midfield, stay organized. Look for the gaps. Well done.
-嘿 进球了 -太好了
-Hey, here we go! -Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
好
Yes!
其他比赛的结果已经出了
All the other results are in.
AFC里士满
AFC Richmond,
经历了史上最惨淡的季初后 奇迹般地
miraculously after a historically dreadful start to the season,
距离第二位只差一个进球
are only one point out of second place.
加油啊 里士满…
Come on, Richmond. Come on, Richmond.
加油 里士满…
如果他们能够追平
If they can somehow salvage a draw,
里士满将回到英超联赛
Richmond will be promoted back to the Premier League.
他们只需要一个放光的时刻 阿尔洛
All they need is one moment of individual brilliance, Arlo.
-加油 里士满 -他们能在吹哨前找到吗
-Come on, Richmond. -Can they find it in time?
加油 里士满
Come on, Richmond. Come on, Richmond.
Come on, Richmond. Come on, Richmond. Come on, Richmond…
荷兰球员的一脚长传
A long ball from the Dutchman.
塔特接球
Tartt is there!
这是里士满的制胜时刻吗
Is this the moment for Richmond?
裁判
Referee!
点球
It's a penalty.
好
Yeah!
-好 -太好了…
-Yes! -Yes! Yes!
应该是塔特负责罚球
We have to think Tartt will be the one to take it.
他这个赛季没有罚丢一粒点球
He hasn't missed a penalty all season.
丹尼
Dani.
你能行的 哥们
You got this, muchacho.
会很有趣的 相信我
It'll be fun. Trust me.
似乎塔特把罚球机会给了罗哈斯
It looks like Tartt is giving the ball to Rojas,
后者很久没有罚过点球了 自从…
who hasn't kicked a penalty since, well…
加油啊 丹尼
Come on, Dani!
（罗哈斯）
加油 丹尼
Let's go, Dani!
Here we go, Dani!
足球就是生命
Football is life.
里士满做到了
Richmond have done it!
凭借这个进球 他们将取得第二位
With that goal, they'll finish in second place
通过第一次努力就回到英超联赛
and will return to the Premier League in their very first attempt.
我们要晋级了…
We are going up! We are going up!
We are going up! Yeah, we are going up!
太好了
Yeah!
结束了
It's all over!
里士满完成了不可思议之举
Richmond have done the impossible
通过坚韧不拔的决心和毅力 最重要的是通过信念
through grit, determination and most of all belief!
我在事业生涯中晋升过一两次 阿尔洛
I was promoted a time or two in my career, Arlo.
这是真正的成就
It's a real achievement.
这是里士满应得的
Richmond deserve this.
但必须提到 他们仍没赢得主要奖杯
They remain a club without a major trophy, it must be said.
但今晚不是这样的感觉
But it won't feel that way tonight.
最终比分：里士满2 布伦特福德2
Final score: Richmond 2, Brentford 2.
快乐又回到内尔森路
And the joy is back at Nelson Road.
-好 -嘿 过来…
-Yeah! -Hey! Come on! Come on!
该死 你这是做什么
Fucking hell! What'd you do that for?
这样我就可以这么做了
So I could do this.
-好耶 -好耶
-Yeah! -Yeah!
好 厉害
Yes! Let's go!
好啊
Yeah!
-好 -好耶
-要喝水吗  -是 谢谢
-You want some water? -Yes, please.
（西伦敦最出色球队）
我们是里士满 至死不渝
We're Richmond till we die
铭记于心 不曾怀疑 我们是里士满 至死不渝
We know we are, we're sure we are We're Richmond till we die
我们是里士满 至死不渝
We're Richmond till we die We're Richmond till we die
铭记于心 不曾怀疑 我们是里士满 至死不渝
We know we are, we're sure we are We're Richmond till we die
我们是里士满 至死不渝
We're Richmond till we die We're Richmond till we die
铭记于心 不曾怀疑 我们是里士满 至死不渝
We know we are, we're sure we are We're Richmond till we die
我们是里士满 至死不渝
We're Richmond till we die
山姆
Sam.
铭记于心 不曾怀疑
We know we are, we're sure we are
我们是里士满 至死不渝
We're Richmond till we die We're Richmond till we die
铭记于心 不曾怀疑 我们是里士满 至死不渝
We know we are, we're sure we are We're Richmond till we die
山姆 嘿…
Sam! Hey. Sammo, hey.
绝佳的表现
Excellent performance.
对 当然 那个进球说明了一切
Yeah, the goal, of course, speaks for itself, yeah.
但你在策略上的控制力 嘿
But your tactical discipline, hey.
这里的人一定会想念你
They are certainly going to miss you around here.
阿库佛先生
Mr. Akufo.
认识你真的很开心 你的邀请也让我感到格外荣幸
I truly enjoyed meeting you, and I'm so flattered by your offer.
但很抱歉 我的答案是“不 谢谢你”
I'm sorry, but my answer is, "No, thank you."
我觉得自己在里士满的旅程还没结束
And I don't believe my time here at Richmond is over.
因此我必须留下
And for that reason, I have to stay.
希望你能理解
I hope you can understand.
你这个尼日利亚混蛋
You Nigerian motherfucker!
约鲁巴垃圾
You Yoruba trash.
你以为自己是谁 敢浪费我的时间
Who the fuck do you think you are, wasting my time?
你就是个平庸之才
You medium-talent piece of shit.
“平庸之才”
"Medium-talent"?
我会用这辈子毁了你 该死的混蛋
I will dedicate my life to destroying you, you fucking asshole!
你别想为尼日利亚国家队踢球
You will never play on the Nigerian national team.
懂吗 臭老二 想都别想
You understand me, pinky-dick? Never!
我会买下你童年的家 在每个房间大便
I will buy your childhood home, and I will take a shit in every room.
然后我会把那里烧毁
And then I will burn the place down.
没错 然后我会坐在那里 吃肯基
Yeah. Then, I will sit there, and I'll eat kenkey,
我会在灰烬上大便 我保证
and I'll poop on the fucking ashes. I promise you this, hey.
好的
Okay.
我永远不会忘记你的无礼
I will never forget this disrespect.
去你的 山姆奥比桑亚
Fuck you, Sam Obisanya.
好大的胆子
Fucking dare!
那混蛋
That dick!
没错
Yes.
大便…
Poop, poop.
好了 大家 嘿 请安静
Okay, y'all. Hey, settle down, y'all.
好的 别急…嘿
Okay, okay. Easy, easy now. Easy. Hey, hey.
大家 别这样 安静一下 听着
Y'all, come on. Calm down, all right? Look--
首先 我想回应一下
Well, right off the cricket bat here, I wanna address the article
我们的好朋友特伦特克里姆先生写的…
written by our good friend, Mr. Trent Crimm from The…
或者说 我想和大家分享
Or rather, I want to share with y'all the truth
关于我近期与焦虑症挣扎的真相
about my recent struggles with anxiety.
以及整体而言 我对于
And, well, my overall concern
人们讨论体育界心理健康问题的方式 有什么担忧
about the way we discuss and deal with mental health in athletics.
嗨 老板 我只是想来为晋级的事恭喜你
Hey, boss. Just wanted to congratulate you on your promotion.
你也是 泰德 喝杯香槟庆祝
You too, Ted. Champagne to celebrate?
-给我一杯水就行了 谢谢 -纯净水还是气泡水
-I'll just take a glass of water, please. -Still or sparkling?
好 纯净水
Yes. Still. Right.
来这里生活之前 我一直以为纯净水
You know, before living here, I used to think still water
意思就是“仍然是水”
was just folks saying it's still water, you know?
即它本来是水 现在仍然是水
Like, it was water, and it continues to remain to be water.
旅行是增长见识的最佳方式
Well, there's no greater education than travel.
可不是嘛
A-freaking-men.
下个赛季一定很有趣 对吧
Well, hey. Next season should be fun, right?
我们将看到一位熟面孔
Well, one that'll include an old friend.
鲁伯特买下了西汉姆联俱乐部
Rupert's bought West Ham United.
是吗
Did he now?
这是个不错的变化
Well, that'll be a nice change.
以后和他相遇都是按时间表来
Having our run-ins with him being scheduled,
和之前他总是偷袭不同
as opposed to his normal sneak attacks.
嗨 瑞贝卡
Hi, Rebecca.
还有教练
And Coach.
抱歉
Sorry.
不 嘿 山姆 请继续 留下 我正打算离开
No. Hey. Sam, go ahead. Stick around. I was getting ready to leave.
-不 泰德 留下 -别走 没事的
-No, Ted. Stay. -No, no, no, no. It's okay.
这样 好吧
Yeah. Okay.
我只想告诉你们两位
I just wanted to let you both know
我决定留在球队
that I've decided to stay.
太棒了 山姆
Hey, that's great, Sam.
是的 听见你这么说很高兴 山姆
Yes. I'm glad to hear that, Sam.
艾德文阿库佛对这个消息怎么看待
How did Edwin Akufo take the news?
心情不太好 他暴跳如雷地走了
Not well. He stormed off.
他已经在回加纳的路上
He's already halfway back to Ghana.
该死 我本来很期待
Oh, shoot. I was really looking forward
和弗兰西斯进行道别握手
to that goodbye handshake from Francis.
我该走了
Well, I should go.
嘿 山姆 我有点好奇
Hey, Sam. I was just curious.
到底你为什么决定留下
What-- Why'd you decide to stay?
我希望答案是因为我对你的感觉
I wish I could say it was because of my feelings for you,
但事实是我认为自己不应再担心 其他人对我的感觉
but the truth is, I think I need to stop worrying about how others feel about me.
我留下是因为这对我本人 和我的个人之旅而言是最好的决定
I'm staying because it's what's best for me and my personal journey.
谢谢
Thank you.
他看着我的时候可能是在对你说话
He might have been talking to you when he was looking at me.
是 我知道 泰德
Yes. I know that, Ted.
-我的天 你这一口真爽快 -是啊
-Oh, hell. You crushed that. -Yeah.
拉索教练
Coach Lasso.
嗨 你在这 我还在担心你
Hey. There he is. I was worried about you.
我以为你骑自行车出事了
I thought you might've been in a bike accident.
其实我不会骑自行车
Actually, I don't know how to ride a bicycle.
真的 我很意外
Really? That surprises me.
为什么 因为我的发型和我的气质
Why? 'Cause of the hair and the whole vibe?
可以这么说
Yeah, I guess so.
为什么你没去记者招待会
Why the heck weren't you at the press conference?
因为我已经不是记者了
Because I am no longer a reporter.
他们发现我泄露了线人身份 于是辞退了我
I was fired when they found out I revealed an anonymous source.
那太糟了 我什么都没说 我保证
Oh, snap. I didn't say anything, I promise.
不 我知道 泰德 是我说的
No, I know, Ted. I did.
我在找不同的东西 更深刻的东西
I'm looking for something different. Deeper.
正如那句老话 人必须追随自己的快乐
Well, as the man says, you gotta follow your bliss, right?
很遗憾你失业了
Sorry you're out of a job.
你知道这让你变成了什么吗
You know what this makes you now, though, right?
特伦特克里姆 独立人
Trent Crimm. Independent.
没错
Yeah.
是的 我父亲也爱说这个笑话
Yeah, yeah. My father made the same joke.
是 听起来他是个很酷的人
Yeah. He sounds like a cool guy.
希望我们还有机会再相遇 特伦特
Well, I hope our paths cross again soon, Trent.
我也是 泰德 我喜欢和你聊天
As do I, Ted. I love our chats.
要载你一程吗
You want a ride?
我比较喜欢走路 不过谢谢你
Well, I prefer to walk, but I appreciate ya.
对了 泰德
And Ted,
祝你下个赛季好运
good luck next season.
该死
Shit.
（五天后）
-这是最后的了  -对 这个和特里希贝尔
-This the last of it? -Yeah. Just these and Trixibelle.
是
Right.
我为你准备了一份 “最后一天当同事”的礼物
I got you a last-day- working-in-the-same-building present.
给
Here.
机票
Airplane tickets?
你为我买了机票
You got me airplane tickets?
去马尔贝拉
To Marbella.
你怎么买到纸版机票的
How did you get actual printed tickets?
我的旅行代理凯西买的 她很守旧
From my travel agent, Kathy. She's old-school.
罗伊 你确定机场仍接受纸版机票吗
Roy, are you sure they still take paper tickets at airports?
飞机是有螺旋桨的那种吗
Like, is the plane gonna have propellers?
天啊 我能在飞机上抽烟吗
Oh, my God. Am I gonna be able to smoke on the flight?
好了 别闹了 你错过了重点
Right, stop it. You are missing the point.
明天 你和我
Tomorrow, you and I
要去海边别墅度过六周
are going to a villa by the sea for six weeks
在你开始在新工作中 大获成功前 先去放松一下
so you can chill out before you start kicking ass in your new job.
这也会是我自12岁以来第一次休假
And I'm going to take the first holiday I've taken since I was 12,
不需要保持身材或做膝盖复健
where I don't have to stay in shape or rehab my fucking knee.
我会吃塔帕斯吃到撑死
I'm gonna gorge myself to death on tapas,
而且整个过程会很漫长
and it will take fucking ages.
宝贝 谢谢你
Babe, thank you.
但我不能去
But I can't go.
什么 为什么
What? Why not?
我不是六周后才开始工作
I don't start work in six weeks.
-我一周前就开始了 -我知道
-I started like a week ago. -Yeah, I know.
所以我确保那地方无线网什么的都有
That's why I made sure the place has got proper Wi-Fi and everything.
你可以收电邮什么的 只不过是在海景阳台上收
You can do all your emails and shit, but from a balcony with a sea view.
罗伊 我很想 但我不能去
Roy, I'd love to. But I can't.
我不能去
I just can't.
但你应该去
But you should go.
我们要分手吗
Are we breaking up?
不 为什么这么说
No. Why would you say that?
当然不是
Of course not.
你要享受一个应得的假日
You are gonna take a well-earned holiday
而我则把自己锁在小黑屋里当工作狂
while I lock myself in a dark room and work nonstop.
我们六周后见
And I'll see you in six weeks.
基莉
Keeley.
罗伊 我爱你
Roy. I love you.
我们会好好的
We'll be fine.
六周后见
I'll see you in six weeks.
（三周后）
恭喜
Congratulations.
它会是什么
What's it gonna be?
一家尼日利亚餐厅
A Nigerian restaurant.
（出售中 查询请联系）
（阿金基德地产公司 房地产销售部）
（两个月后）
-快点 速度加快 上 -教练 先生
-Move! I want it faster! Go! -Coach! Sir!
-快 -教练
-Move! -Coach!
-下一个 快 -先生
-Next. Go. -Sir!
-快点 -教练
-Move it! -Coach!
-快 -先生
-Go! -Sir!
（必威）
-快 上 -教练
-Move! Go! -Coach!
-快点 上 -教练 先生
-Move! Go! -Coach! Sir!
-快点 -教练
-Move! -Coach!